lzhgzhj收藏
艺术家
The Artist
我不会说的！我一个字都不会说的！！！
I won't talk !
Iwon't say a word !!!
说！
Speak !
在银幕后请保持安静
PLEASE BE SILENT BEHIND
THE SCREEN
自由的乔治亚万岁！！！
Long live free Georgia !!!
你会为此付出代价
I will get you for this.
拉瑞纳剧院
俄国韵事
乔治・瓦伦汀
这个女孩是谁？
WHO'S THAT GIRL?
“每个人都在问，她到底是谁？”
"That's The Question On
Everyone's Lips, Who Indeed"
基诺电影公司
KINOGRAPH STUDIOS
群众演员试演前必须登记
EXTRAS MUST SIGN-IN
BEFORE AUDITIONS
听好了！要三个会跳舞的女孩！
Listen up ! Three girls
who can dance !
我叫米勒，佩琵・米勒
The name's Miller.
Peppy Miller !
克利夫顿，去珠宝店
给我妻子买件漂亮首饰，弥补她一下
Clifton, go to the jewelry store.
Get Somthing nice for my wife.
To make it up to her.
就因为你瞎胡闹
到第五页上他们才提到我们的电影
With all your nonsense,
they don't mention our movie until page 5 !
你这是要去哪儿，小姐？
我们可有个电影要拍
Where are you going, Miss?
We have a picture to shoot.
德国韵事
"A GERMAN AFFAIR"
场记牌：基诺电影公司 片名：德国韵事
第20场第2次 导演：奥托・瓦格曼
化妆室
DRESSING ROOMS
墙上海报：芳心窃贼
如果你想成为一名演员
你得与众不同一点
If you want to be an actress,
you need to have something the others don't.
镜上字：谢谢你
乔治・瓦伦汀：人见人爱的男人
佩琵・米勒扮演伊萨多拉小姐
我有样东西要给你看
I have something to show you.
能给我拿把椅子吗？！
May I have my chair ?!
嘿，你又不是真的拿破仑
你只是个群众演员
Hey, you're not Napoleon.
You're just an extra !
试音
康斯坦斯・格雷
SOUND TEST
Constance Gray
《罗密欧和朱丽叶》
5/12/1929
in
Romeo & Juliet
5 / 12 / 29
别笑，乔治！
这是未来的趋势
Don't laugh, George !
That's the future.
如果这就是未来，那你去玩吧！
If that's the future,
you can have it !
基诺电影公司停止所有默片生产
只拍摄有声片
你和我已经落伍了，乔治
这个世界开始说话了
You and I belong to another era, George.
The world is talking now.
观众需要新面孔，会说话的面孔
People want new faces,
talking faces.
我也不希望这样
但观众需要新鲜玩意儿，观众永远是对的
I wish it wasn't like this, but the public
wants fresh meat and the public is never wrong.
观众来就是看我的动作的
他们永远也不需要听我的声音！
I'm the one people come to see.
They never needed to hear me !
拍你的有声电影去吧
我将拍一部伟大的电影
我不希望你帮任何忙！
Make your talking movies. I'll make a great movie.
And it's not like I need you for that !
基诺影业的新面孔们
新玩意儿…
Fresh meat...
真巧，我刚刚还想起你呢
我和基诺电影公司签约了！
What a coincidence, I was just thinking
about you. I signed with Kinograph !
也许现在我们能在一起拍新电影了！
Maybe now we'll do
anorher picture together !
佩琵
宅电：H000508
花瓶！
Toys !
杂志名：电影领地
支票：1000美金   好莱坞联合银行
场记牌：导演兼制片：乔治・瓦伦汀
片名：爱之泪
拍摄第68天
10月25日隆重上映
爱之泪
佩琵・米勒 美人痣
我不是傀儡，我是个艺术家！
I'm not a puppet, I'm an artist !
对乔治・瓦伦汀认为说话片不够严肃
Talkies are not serious
for George Valentin
从演员到导演兼制片人
乔治・瓦伦汀挑战自我
From Actor to Director-producer
The George Valentin's challenge
佩琵・米勒：美人痣闪耀
PEPPY MILLER
The girl you'll Love to Love
佩琵・米勒
让你情不自禁的女孩
有声片多有趣，观众会爱上
千万别错过佩琵・米勒
伟大的女演员，有声片的新星
你会爱上她，会说话的佩琵闪亮登场
佩琵会说话的新面孔，佩琵・米勒发出爱之声！
佩琵・米勒 小城的最爱！
我们必须谈谈，乔治
We have to talk, George
为什么你不愿意说话？
Why do you refuse to talk ?
我不快乐，乔治
I'm unhappy, George.
世上的人都不快乐
So are millions of us.
你的电影明天才上映
但你已经是好莱坞的新宠！
Your movie doesn't come out until tomorrow
and you're already Hollywood's new sweetheart !
你对此有何解释呢？
How do you explain that ?
我不知道
也许是因为我开口说话，观众能够听到我
I don't know. Maybe because I talk
and the audience can hear me.
观众厌倦了老演员们在镜头前夸张地挤眉弄眼
People are tired of old actors mugging
at the camera to be understood.
旧的不去，新的不来
给年轻一代让路吧！
Out with the old, in with the new.
Make way for the young !
这就是生活！
That's life !
我已经为你让路了
I've made way for you.
股市崩溃
STOCK MARKET
CRASH
报纸标题：调查者报
黑色星期四，股市崩溃
看上去我们好像已经破产了
It looks like we've gone bust.
除非电影能卖座…
Unless the movie is a big hit...
永别了，诺玛
我从来没爱过你
Farewell Norma I never loved you.
美人痣
佩琵・米勒
Beauty Spot
PEPPY MILLER
我们之间结束了，乔治，给你两个星期
收拾好你的东西，搬出这所房子，多丽丝
It's over George, you have two weeks to collect
your souvenirs together and get out of the hose.
Doris
附言：你应该去看看《美人痣》
P.S you should go see Beauty Spot
你好，我想告诉你，我…
Hello. I wanted to talk to you. I...
我刚刚看了《爱之泪》
I just saw Tears of Love.
你是来要求退票的吗？
And you want a refund ?
挤眉弄眼没那么多吗？
Not too much mugging ?
不，我…昨天晚上的事我很抱歉
我并不是那个意思…
No. I... I'm sorry about last night.
I didn't mean what I said...
但你是对的，给年轻一代让路…
But you were right.
Make way for the young...
见到你很荣幸，我的父亲是你的忠实影迷
It's an honor to meet you.
My father is a big fan.
好了，我们要走了，我会打电话给你的
OK. We're going now.
I'll call you soon.
送我回家，我想一个人待着
Take me home.
I want to be alone.
报纸：花样新闻
佩琵・米勒
洛杉矶姑娘，天下有谁不知？
PAWN SHOP
当铺
我多久没付你薪水了，克利夫顿？
How long has it been since I
last paid you, Clifton ?
一年了，先生
One year, sir.
你被解雇了
You're fired.
我不是在开玩笑，克利夫顿，你被解雇了
I'm not kidding, Clifton.
You're fired.
车归你了，另外去找份工作吧
Keep the car. And find
yourself another job.
我不需要别的工作
I don't want another job.
今晚拍卖著名好莱坞影星乔治・瓦伦汀的物品
To Night AUCTION of famed
Hollywood actor George Valentin
恭喜！全卖光了，你什么都没剩下！
Congratulations ! It's all sold,
you've got nothing left !
商店招牌：孤独之星
守护天使
GUARDIAN ANGEL
佩琵・米勒最新电影！
The new PEPPY MILLER motion picture !
打扰了，能耽搁你一会儿吗？
Excuse me, may I
trouble you one moment ?
要是他能说话就好了！
If only he could talk !
瞧瞧你变成什么样了…
Look what's become of you...
你这个愚蠢的家伙，你这个骄傲的家伙！
You've been stupid !
You've been proud !
回来，你这个失败的家伙！！！
GET BACK HERE, YOU LOSER !!!
噢，我的上帝！这是乔治・瓦伦汀！
Oh my God ! That's
George Valentin !
我去把车开来！
I'll get my car !
我得说句话，是这条狗救了他的命！
I'll say one thing, he
owes his life to that dog !
座位背后名字：
制作人 佩琵・米勒 编剧
电影明星遭遇火灾，幸免于难
Film Actor Survives Fire
我们准备好了，去叫米勒小姐吧
We're ready. Go get Miss Miller.
他已经脱离危险了，他现在需要休息
He's out of danger.
He needs rest now.
他的手紧抓着这个，拿都拿不下来
He was clutching this.
It was hard to get it away from him.
他可以到我家里休养吗？
You think he could rest
at my house ?
我必须九点到片场
有一个很重要的镜头要拍
I have to be on the set at nine o'clock.
We're shooting a very important scene.
想象一下！《爱的火花》
乔治・瓦伦汀和佩琵・米勒主演
Just think of it ! SPARKLE OF LOVE,
starring George Valentin and Peppy Miller
乔治是个默片演员，他现在什么也不是了
George is a silent movie actor.
He's a nobody now.
你要干什么？
What are you doing ?
我不干了
要么他，要么我
I won't work anymore.
It's either him or me.
我是说，要么他和我一起！要么一个都没有！
What I mean is, it's him AND me !
Or it's neither of us !
嘿，我这是在威胁你！明白了吗？
Hey, I'm blackmailing you !
Get it ?
好吧，把该死的剧本给他吧
All right, send him the damn screenplay.
我现在为米勒小姐打工
I work for Miss Miller now.
她又一次默默关心你
Once again, she's looking out for you.
请听我一句劝，先生，别让骄傲冲昏你的头脑
米勒小姐是个好人，相信我
Beware of your pride, if I may say so sir.
Miss Miller is a good person, believe me.
克利夫顿！
CLIFTON !
嘭！
BANG !
我感觉很糟糕，我只是想帮助你，照顾你…
I feel so bad. I only wanted to help you,
take care of you...
只要你肯让我帮助你，乔治・瓦伦汀
If only you would let me help you,
George Valentin.
这不可能，佩琵
我已经落伍了，没人想听我说话
It's impossible, Peppy.
I'm washed up. No one wants to see me speak.
正是这件事我们可以试试
相信我
There is one thing we could try.
Trust me.
棒极了！
Perfect !
漂亮
Beautiful
你们能再跳一段吗？
Would you give me just one more?
荣幸之至
With pleasure
开拍…
Action...